by RentAnAdviser.com
Today I don′t feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don′t feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
′Cause today I swear I am
not doing anything
Uh I am gona kick my feet
up and stare at the fan
Turn the t.v. on
Throw my hand in my pants
Nobody′s gon′ tell me I cant‚ no
I will be loungin′ on the couch
just chillin′ in my snuggie
Flip to MTV so they can teach
me how to Dougie
′Cause in my castle I
am the freakin′ man
Oh
Yes I said it
I said it
I said it ′cause I can
Today I don′t feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don′t feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
′Cause today I swear I am
not doing anything
Nothing at all
Ooh hoo ooh hoo
Hoo ooh ooh
Nothing at all
Ooh hoo ooh hoo
Hoo ooh ooh
Tomorrow I will wake up do some p90x
met a really nice girl have
some really nice sex
And She is gona scream
out this is great
I might mess around and
get my college degree
I bet my old man will
be so proud of me
But sorry pops you′ll
just have to wait
Oh
Yes I said it
I said it
I said it ′cause I can
Today I don′t feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don′t feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
′Cause today I swear I am
not doing anything
No I ain′t gona comb my hair
′Cause I ain′t goin′ anywhere
No no no no no no no no no oh
I will just strut in my birthday suit
And let everything hang loose
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh‚ today I don′t feel
like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don′t feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
′Cause today I swear I am
not doing anything
Nothing at all
Ooh hoo ooh hoo
Hoo ooh ooh
Nothing at all
Ooh hoo ooh hoo
Hoo ooh ooh
Nothing at all
www.RentAnAdviser.com