by RentAnAdviser.com
When the days are cold
And the cards all fold
And the saints we see
Are all made of gold
When your dreams all fail
And the ones we hail
Are the worst of all
And the blood′s run stale
I wanna hide the truth
I wanna shelter you
But with the beast inside
There′s nowhere we can hide
No matter what we breed
We still are made of greed
This is my kingdom come
When you feel my heat
Look into my eyes
It is where my demons hide
Don′t get too close
It is dark inside
It is where my demons hide
At the curtains call
It is the last of all
When the lights fade out
All the sinners crawl
So they dug your grave
And the masquerade
Will come calling out
At the mess You have made
Don′t wanna let you down
But I am‚ hell bound
Though this is all for you
Don′t wanna hide the truth
No matter what we breed
We still are made of greed
This is my kingdom come
When you feel my heat
Look into my eyes
It is where my demons hide
Don′t get too close
It is dark inside
It is where my demons hide
They say It is what you make
I say It is up to fate
It is woven in my soul
I need to let you go
Your eyes‚ they shine so bright
I wanna save that light
I can′t escape this now
Unless you show me how
When you feel my heat
Look into my eyes
It is where my demons hide
Don′t get too close
It is dark inside
It is where my demons hide
www.RentAnAdviser.com